<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="./css/xml.css" type="text/css"?>
<aaaa>
    <h1>
        Terms and Conditions
    </h1>
    <p1>
        1. Prevent Site Abuse
    </p1>
    <p>
        By accessing and using The Retro Rack website, you agree to comply with our guidelines on proper site usage. Acceptable actions include respectful interaction with our platform and other users. Unacceptable behaviors include, but are not limited to:

- Spamming or sending unsolicited messages.
- Using bots or automated systems to access or interfere with the site.
- Posting defamatory, offensive, or harmful content.
- Attempting to compromise the security of the website.
- Engaging in fraudulent activities or impersonation.

Violations of these terms may result in the suspension or termination of your account and access to our services.
    </p>
    <p1>
        2. Limitations of Liability
    </p1>
    <p>
        The Retro Rack strives to provide accurate product descriptions and high-quality thrifted apparel. However, we are not liable for:

- Personal injury arising from the use of our products.
- Loss of profits or business interruptions.
- Computer malfunctions due to accessing our site.
- Misinterpretations of product information.
- Warranty issues beyond those explicitly stated.

By purchasing from our site, you acknowledge and accept these limitations of liability.
    </p>
    <p1>
        3. Protection of Intellectual Property
    </p1>
    <p>
        All content on The Retro Rack website, including but not limited to logos, images, graphics, and text, is the property of The Retro Rack and is protected by copyright and trademark laws. Unauthorized use of our intellectual property is prohibited. Users may not reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works from our content without explicit written permission from us.
    </p>
    <p1>
        4. Minimizing Disputes
    </p1>
    <p>
        We aim to provide a clear and transparent shopping experience. In the event of any disputes, we encourage customers to contact our customer service team for resolution. If a dispute cannot be resolved amicably, it will be handled in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. By agreeing to these terms, you consent to the dispute resolution procedures outlined herein.
    </p>
    <p1>
        5. Establishing Trust
    </p1>
    <p>
        At The Retro Rack, we value your trust and strive for transparency in all our operations. These Terms and Conditions are designed to clearly outline the rules of using our site, helping to prevent misunderstandings. We are committed to providing a secure and enjoyable shopping experience, and we encourage you to reach out with any questions or concerns.
    </p>
</aaaa>